Words are upset, oh God, oh God, the heart is also upset, everything is scattered, scattered, scattered, the cold is upset, the silence is hidden, how do I ask, how do I ask, come, come
Рутхи хэ шабд рабба рабба, дил бхи хэ рутха, саб кучу хэ бикхра бикхра бикхра, сару тхарутха, чипнаи чуп хэ ланджал, мол каисе ве ладжа, мол каисе ве, а джа а джа
Series
Серия
Music is not silent, come, come, music
Музыка не молчи, а джа джа музыка
My dear, don't worry, I told you, I will handle everything
Мера лорая, хэир, ты не беспокойся. Я же сказал, я всё улажу.
Love
Любовь
You are so good
Ты такой хороший
You take such good care of me, love me so much even knowing that I can't see, I am blind, you handle my home, my office, and support me in every way, thank you so much, oh there's no need to thank
Ты так заботишься обо мне, так любишь меня, зная, что я не вижу, я слепая. Ты заботишься о моём доме, о моём офисе и во всём так поддерживаешь меня. Спасибо тебе большое. Да что тут за спасибо, мы же не разные. Кто, если не я, будет заботиться о твоём бизнесе?
we are not separate, if I don't handle your business, who will
Ладно, принесу для тебя файл, садись.
Come, I'll bring the final for you, sit
Сейчас принесу для тебя файл.
I'll bring the final for you
Я принесу для тебя файл.
My name is doctor James
Меня зовут доктор Джеймс
I'm the eye specialist
Я специалист по глазам
it's our first time so don't worry I'm a friend of your husband
это наш первый раз, так что не волнуйтесь, я друг вашего мужа
OK if you're ready let's head into the clinic
Хорошо, если вы готовы, давайте пройдем в клинику
Please have a seat
Пожалуйста, садитесь
Sorry but your husband will have to wait outside
Извините, но вашему мужу придется подождать снаружи
I need to focus on my patient oh OK
Мне нужно сосредоточиться на пациенте. О, хорошо
thank you
спасибо
OK zombies so how long have you not been feeling well
Хорошо, зомби, как долго вы плохо себя чувствуете?
10 years
10 лет
10 years I see and can you see these numbers on the blackboard here
10 лет, понятно. И можете ли вы видеть эти цифры на доске?
OK look at your eyes
Хорошо, взгляните на ваши глаза
please let me take a quick
позвольте мне быстро посмотреть
OK
Хорошо
thank you
спасибо
One more check here how many fingers am I holding up
Еще одна проверка здесь, сколько пальцев я показываю?
No no it's only one figure OK
Нет, нет, это только один палец, хорошо
I just need to check your temperature
Мне просто нужно проверить вашу температуру
Forgotten my thermometer
Забыл термометр
could you take your mask off please and open your mouth
не могли бы вы снять маску и открыть рот, пожалуйста